southwestvacations.com 2018-10-07

# Privacy & Security Policy - Southwest Vacations

## E-mail addresses, registration, and my account

The e-mail address you provide when you subscribe to Southwest Vacations' e-mail specials will not be shared with any third parties. If you wish to subscribe or unsubscribe from our e-mail list, please go to the [my account](https://res.southwestvacations.com/Account/RetrieveLogin.aspx?ctl=A) page. 

If you utilize our "e-mail a friend" function, we will not collect your friend's personal information without their express consent. 

Any personal information you provide when you register or customize your website using the my account settings will be utilized for Southwest Vacations marketing purposes only. This information will help us provide the vacations that interest you. The information will not be shared with any third parties. 

## Billing information and vacation purchases

Information provided to purchase your Southwest Vacations package will be utilized to complete your transaction. The information will only be shared with vendors and financial institutions necessary to complete your reservation.

## Security

We utilize Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to encrypt and protect your personal information. SSL keeps the data private and confidential between your computer and Southwest Vacations. This technology makes it safe to transmit your credit card number over the internet.

Look for two security icons, the "s" after "http" in the address line and the lock in the top menu bar and bottom status bar of your browser. 

If purchasing a gift card, you'll notice the secure URL listed is secure02.com, not southwestvacations.com. This is because Southwest Vacations stores gift card purchases on a separate secure server. Rest assured, your secure transaction is with Southwest Vacations.

## Passwords 

When you purchase a Southwest Vacations package online, you are asked to create a password so you can access your vacation itinerary online. When you assign your password, we strongly advise you keep it guarded and do not share it with anyone else.

When you register on southwestvacations.com, you will also be asked to create a password. This password will allow you to login and access your account. We will keep this password on file and can provide you with your login password if you forget it.

## Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. This allows our system to recognize your browser and remember select items such as your preferred origin airport. We do not utilize cookies to save your credit card number. You must type your credit card number in each time you purchase travel with us online.

We also utilize cookies to track the effectiveness of our online marketing. This data is used for promotional and marketing purposes only and the reports we generate do not recognize any information specific to your individual computer. This information allows us to target our marketing dollars to the most effective channels, thus keeping our costs low and our vacation package prices affordable for you. 

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

## Policy changes

Southwest Vacations reserves the right to modify its privacy policy at any time in our sole discretion without notice. 

## Opt-in and opt-out

You may choose to receive vacation information when you create your account. If you decide you no longer wish to receive information from Southwest Vacations, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link in any of our e-mail specials.

## Contact information

If you still have questions about our privacy policy, please [contact us](https://www.southwestvacations.com/generalinformation/customer-care-and-travel-information).
